42photo.com 2005-04-06

# 42Photo.com Computers and Electronics

**42ND STREET PHOTO PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This confirms that 42photo.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users� trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact [http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html](http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html). ****

**Information Collection and Use**

42nd Street Photo is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  42nd Street Photo collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  

**Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. 

**  
Order **  
We request information from the user on our order form.  Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).  This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer�s orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user�s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.  The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing  
** We use an outside shipping company to ship orders. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links  
** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we 42nd Street Photo are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security  
** This website takes every precaution to protect our users� information.  When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just �surfing�.  To learn more about SSL, follow this link

[https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/89d16c88a39f4c4137227222b27baa29](https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/eacaa94e20e0a1eac8e44a02e1b0567a)

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users� information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk.  When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers� information is protected.  Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@42photo.com](mailto:security@42photo.com). 

**  
Site and Service Updates**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. **  
**We also send the user site and order confirmation e-mails. Members are not able to un-subscribe from site announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:  
** If a user�s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update user�s personal data provided to us.  This can be done at the member information page by clicking on update profile. 

**Choice/Opt-out     
**  
42photo.com does not send users any promotional marketing materials or newsletters. We only send a one time welcoming e-mail to verify password and username and order  
confirmation e-mails.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Notification of Changes  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. ~~~~

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Phone: 212-594-6565

Fax: 212-594-7508

Email: [privacy@42photo.com](mailto:privacy@42photo.com)

Postal Address: 378 5th Avenue New York, NY 10018 (35th & 36th Street)

|   
---|---
